### Contact

marissag296@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/marissagutierrez-8usfca (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Spanish

Creativity

Interpersonal Skill

### Languages

Spanish (Native or Bilingual) English (Native or Bilingual)

#### Certifications

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

Clinical Nurse Leader (CNL)
Certification

Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers (BLS)

Registered Nurse

Neonatal Resuscitation Program

# Marissa Gutierrez, MSN, RN, CNL

Registered Nurse at Zuckerberg San Francisco General Hospital and Trauma Center

San Francisco

# Summary

Compassionate, driven, and bilingual (English/Spanish) New Graduate Registered Nurse with more than 4 years of healthcare experience serving patients of all ages in hospitals and clinical settings.

My education and diverse clinical experience have broadened my skillset and taught me to be a highly adaptable lifelong learner, and a team player to promote positive patient outcomes.

My passion is to serve my community by providing accessible and respectful patient-centered care while collaborating with the healthcare team to foster a therapeutic healing environment.

# Experience

Zuckerberg San Francisco General Hospital and Trauma Center Registered Nurse February 2020 - Present (7 months)

Trusted Child Care (acq by Care.com) Child Care Provider June 2019 - February 2020 (9 months)

University of San Francisco Nursing Tutor January 2019 - May 2019 (5 months) San Francisco Bay Area

St. Rose Hospital
Unit Assistant (Labor & Delivery)
August 2016 - June 2017 (11 months)

Pacific Coast Psychiatric Associates Medical Receptionist September 2015 - April 2016 (8 months)

Citizen Schools
AmeriCorps Teaching Fellow
September 2014 - June 2015 (10 months)
Oakland, CA

UC Davis Medical Center
Pediatric Specialty Clinic-Intern
September 2013 - March 2014 (7 months)
Sacramento, California Area

Child Family Health International
Global Health Intern
September 2012 - December 2012 (4 months)
Oaxaca de Juárez Area, Mexico

Shadowed health care professionals in General Surgery, Pediatrics, Labor and Delivery units, as well as, Primary Care clinics. Applied spanish skills in a clinical setting by facilitating educational community health programs for up to 40 High school students.

Ninos Sanos, Familia Sana (Healthy Kids, Healthy Families) UC Davis Research Intern February 2012 - June 2012 (5 months) San Joaquin, CA

Conducted surveys to the families about their past medical history and eating habits at home, and translated the surveys to Spanish speaking families. Purpose of the study was to implement a community-based intervention that promotes healthy eating habits and physical activity among Latino children living in Central Valley, to help reduce childhood obesity rates and ethnic disparities. Research funded by the USDA Agricultural and Food Research Initiative

## Education

University of San Francisco
Master's Entry- Master of Science in Nursing (MSN), Clinical Nurse
Leader · (2017 - 2019)

University of California, Davis

Bachelor's degree, Human Development & Chicano Studies · (2009 - 2014)

Mount Eden High School (2005 - 2009)